One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Zou
Dressrosa
Royal Palace
I can't find any of the manifests they used for trafficking,
but it was all clearly stolen by somebody.
I thought so.
All the weapons and explosives that were left behind were stolen after the incident.
There was quite a bit, too.
Cipher Pol, Aigis Zero
The handiwork of some organization, surely.
The Navy was panicking about it as well.
The Revolutionary Army, perhaps?
Yeah, who else would it be?
Return at once.
They're thorns in my side, I swear.
You're absolutely right, boss!
Just like you, as a matter of fact.
Wow! That's harsh!
So where are you heading to next, Straw Hat?
This was a land of tragedy.
Dark strings were woven, one after another.
Despite the countless tragedies that befell them,
they manage to hold back their tears for now,
and music plays on...
Oh, yeah!
Music that rings out to the rhythm of clapping hands.
The curtain is drawn after the long, sad,
nameless performance without fanfare.
Then, words of truth reach the ears of the audience.
Their king has returned,
and with peace in their future, all is well.
I have a proposition for you all.
Um, thank you for the introduction.
I am the Tontattan Chief, Gancho!
Standing next to me is my daughter.
I am Mansherry!
So cute!
You want us to make this, Leo-kun?
That's right!
We're counting on you!
The world conference, the Reverie, is this year.
It will be here before we know it.
And it seems like every country has already begun their preparations.
Father!
Rebecca said she's coming over to cook for us this afternoon.
Oh, is that so? What about Kyros?
He's coming too, of course.
I see, I see. It's been so long since we've dined...
as a family.
Visitors to this kingdom will be shocked by a certain sight.
Ham, please!
Oh, hello there,
Rebecca, Mansherry!
They are blending in with the town,
living side-by-side with humans.
Hey, hey.
We haven't even rebuilt our own homes yet!
No, no! This is priority number one!
Visitors will be amazed at the sight of these adorable gnomes.
This is the kingdom of love, passion, and fairies...
You're right. The statues come first!
Darn right!
... Dressrosa.
When we're finished transporting our prisoner,
I'll be going on a journey.
Naval Fleet
A journey, you say?
Without the heads of Straw Hat and Law,
I cannot set foot in a Navy base, so...
So stubborn...
If you'd just apologize,
Sakazuki can save face.
No!
And why not?
I have my own honor to save as well.
For crying out loud...
Fujitora...
He's an idiot, you know, Tsuru-san.
This was his last chance.
If he'd sided with me and
helped rid me of that bunch of brats,
things wouldn't have ended up this way.
I was holding the reins.
The reins attached to the monsters of the world.
You shouldn't have removed me.
I'm extremely certain
you'll all come to regret this.
Don't pawn off that pathetic crap on me.
There is no "if".
It's insanity to even consider it.
This was the only possible outcome.
You lost.
Oh, how can I ever win against you?
It takes one to know one.
What do you think lies ahead
in the world of pirates?
I'll answer your question with another question.
What do you think those monsters you unleashed will do...
without the "food" I supplied them?
Is there anyone sailing these seas at this moment that's truly at the top rung of the ladder?
Who rules these seas?
Is it one of the Four Emperors of the Seas?
Or the Seven Warlords who cunningly roam these waters?
Perhaps those brats
from the Worst Generation?
Or, no...
Surely it's the Navy, that military force of justice,
that's conquering the seas!
And then there are some strong individuals we must keep a close eye on...
in the Revolutionary Army,
the allies of the people.
The family of "D" has been hiding
within the shadows of history.
When and where will they appear?
Who sides with who?
Who betrays who?
Tell the Celestial Dragons
in the Holy Land of Mariejoa this:
"You will all be brought low, to the very ground!"
It's been 25 years since Gold Roger explored the Grand Line in its entirety.
His arch-nemesis, Whitebeard,
never took the throne.
He merely stood before it and took the reins.
So what happens now?
The number of pirates is swelling,
and there's just one seat
that remains empty!
You understand what I'm getting at, right?
It's beginning.
The greatest struggle for supremacy ever...
in pirate history!
The mast has caught fire!
Put it out!
Are we headed to Impel Down?
I hate to ask, but would you mind delivering the daily newspaper to me?
That way, I won't be bored.
There are four battleships.
But their crew looks insanely formidable.
Are they looking to destroy a country?
So much force for a simple escort mission.
That must speak to
how great Doflamingo-sama is!
It'll be impossible to take back Joker.
Captain Jack, shall we return?
Why?
Huh?
You moron!
We're going through with it!
Huh?!
Who do you think I am?!
Meanwhile, Luffy's Group
Barto Club Pirate Ship
The Going Luffy-Senpai
Does this look right to you guys?!
Why does it look like Luffy'd be on this ship rather than ours!
Just hearing that makes my day!
That wasn't a compliment!
And now, the thing we're most thrilled about at this very moment...
In the direction this Vivre Card is pointing,
it's the real Luffy-senpai!
Welcome aboard!
Thank you once again for boarding our ship!
Boss, he's glowing so brightly!
I can barely see him!
Me too!
So the whole crew's the same way?
Anyway, it was awful nice of Sabo to make a Vivre Card of me.
Here, I had a Vivre Card made from Luffy, just in case.
Oh? When'd you have time for that?
I'll be taking a piece.
Oh, that's the great Sabo-senpai for ya!
He's so thoughtful and strong! Whatta guy!
I ain't gonna be no follower of yours, but...
I'll take a scrap, just in case.
Bellamy!
We'll help ourselves to some, too.
Well, here's where we part ways.
See ya soon, our boss,
Straw Hat Luffy!
Later, guys!
Man, I had so much fun partyin'!
I think they grew on me a bit!
Bartolomeo, hurry up and take us to Zou.
Who d'ya think yer talkin' to...
We're counting on you.
Aye, aye!
Leave it to us!
Right, you lot!
Set course fer Zou, full speed ahead!
Aye, aye!
I wonder if Sanji and the others ever made it to the island safely?
Nami was with them,
so I'm sure they were fine navigation-wise,
but Big Mom's ship
was hot on their tail...
It's worrying, indeed.
Hey, Luffy.
Our bounties've gone up!
Huh, really?!
Oh, you didn't know?
Well, I've got wanted posters of
the whole crew in my room, so after you, please!
Please!
Alright, I'll go!
Hey, Trafalgar.
I threw yours out already,
but your bounty shot up to five hundred mil.
Oh, thanks. I couldn't care less.
Feast your eyes on them,
if you would please!
You f-framed them?!
The autographs you gave me earlier
are there too!
Well then, let's start with Straw Hat Luffy-senpai!
"Me" "To Bartolomeo" Kanji for "Sword" "To Brothers" "Nico Robin" in Hiragana
His bounty: 500 million belly!
500 million! Yeah!
"Straw Hat" Luffy
Bounty: 500,000,000 Belly
Next, Pirate Hunter Zoro-senpai!
320 million belly!
"Pirate Hunter" Zoro
Bounty: 320,000,000 Belly
Hey, got any swill?
Demon Child Nico Robin-senpai!
130 million belly!
"Demon Child" Nico Robin
Bounty: 130,000,000 Belly
Oh, no. It's gone up.
The Cyborg, Franky-senpai!
94 million belly!
"Cyborg" Franky
Bounty: 94,000,000 Belly
Short by that much!
On top of that,
the picture's of the General Franky...
God Usopp-senpai! 200 million belly!
"God" Usopp
Bounty: 200,000,000 Belly
I'm unmasked and the price is outrageous!
I'm a marked man!
But that makes me so happy!
Still, that picture is awful!
Hey, screw you!
How did you get your bounty that high?!
Even my own crewmate's trying to kill me!
I'm the only one at less than a hundred mil!
It's so unfair!
Wait, wait a sec! Look closer!
There're still Nami and the others!
Black Leg Sanji-senpai, 177 million belly!
"Black Leg" Sanji
Bounty: 177,000,000 Belly
Oh, his poster isn't a sketch anymore!
Tsk! That's boring.
The last one was funnier.
Cat Burglar Nami-senpai, 66 million belly!
"Cat Burglar" Nami
Bounty: 66,000,000 Belly
When the hell'd she
have her picture taken again?!
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper-senpai!
A hundred belly!
"Cotton Candy Lover" Chopper
Bounty: 100 Belly
There are no words
that would cheer him up.
The Soul King, Brook-senpai, 83 million belly!
"The Soul King" Brook
Bounty: 83,000,000 Belly
That's like a poster for his concert!
'Cept for the people who stood out and showed just how dangerous they could be in the recent incident,
everybody went up by 50 million!
Ours have gone up by 50 million too.
But...
Lookit that fer a sec.
The bounty on Black Leg Sanji-senpai's head went up by a weird amount,
and what's written here
is even weirder.
"Only alive"?
It's hail!
They're big! Watch out!
– Huh?!
– It punched a hole in the deck!
Luffy-senpai and everybody!
Get inside now!
What're you talking about?!
We'll help you!
Which way should we turn?!
Who's your navigator?!
Give us directions!
Oh, we don't have a navigator
since we were a land-based gang originally.
What?!
You're in the New World, you know?!
Hello, Grandma? It's me, Gambia!
The thing is, huge hail
just started falling on us.
Whenever we're in trouble,
we call Grandma in our hometown.
I see! So she knows about the sea!
Hey, I got it!
We have some chewing gum
stuck to the deck, right?
Yeah, and we didn't know what to do!
Wrap the hailstone in cloth
and cool the gum to peel it off!
Alright!
It came off surprisingly easily!
We don't need that sort of wisdom now!
But...
See! You got hit!
Apply sugar to his lump, she says!
Enough with her wisdom!
Oh no! This ship's gonna sink!
Nami, help us!
We had so many ships to choose from
but we got on board the wrong one!
I guess we gotta deal with this ourselves!
If only we had the Sunny's equipment!
It's so lively.
Why aren't you using your barrier?!
What?! Well, Grandma says,
"You'll regret it if you defy nature!"
If you're so scared, get back on land!
Are they for real?!
Guys! We have the Straw Hats
who don't even fear god
and that's like getting help
from a thousand people!
Our appreciation rains down
like hail and snow pellets!
How have you guys
survived until now?!
I'm so happy!
You do something too, you fools!
The A.O. Pirates,
formerly of the Whitebeard Pirates,
Navy Headquarters
have been wiped out.
Is it that guy again?
Yes, it's the Warlord, Edward Weevil.
Kizaru (Borsalino)
The Navy HQ Admiral
How many captains who used
to work under Whitebeard...
... have been brought down?
16 captains, sir.
Like the other cases, it
seems like they were blown up
along with the town after
some kind of argument.
The casualties are about 600.
He always causes a lot of collateral damage.
Even though he's the Warlord,
we can't just overlook it.
What should we do?
He says he's "Whitebeard" Edward
Newgate's biological son
and that makes him special but many
people aren't buying it...
Well, it doesn't matter
to us if it's true or not.
Wall Reads as "Unclear Justice".
Whoever his father is, he has one sure value.
As a pirate, he's overwhelmingly strong.
Pretty much like Whitebeard
when he was young.
That's the only thing they have in common.
A week after leaving Dressrosa...
Oh, it's too foggy. I can't see ahead.
You guys are getting seasick too often!
How could you call yourselves pirates?!
Chewing gum... Chewing gum...
It'll make it a little better, Grandma said.
Oh, that's why there is gum
stuck everywhere on this ship!
What a riot!
Boss! I see something at two o'clock!
What is it?!
In the dense fog,
there's a mountain or a monster...
I hope there's no monster
that can be mistaken for a mountain!
But it looks like it's moving slowly...
You're just drunk, you...
If it's a mountain that moves, let's go!
No, idiot! Anyway, what we gotta do now
is get out of this foggy
maze as soon as possible!
Otherwise, we'll hit a reef and capsize!
Wait, God.
Did you call me "God"? I'm flattered!
I'm a man of 200 million and I'm flattered!
I'm sure even the Navy admirals
are aware of you now.
Look. The Vivre Card is
pointing towards that.
Oh, you're right!
That means your friends are there!
Usopp, you look sick.
Do you want chewing gum too?
I've been refusing to face the reality...
I heard...
... Zou blocks out invaders
with dense fog and an adverse current.
There are headwinds too!
Take in the sails! We'll row it forward!
Roger that...
Hey! That's not how you respond!
Is this the island, Zou?!
No, that's strange!
This is no good!
Let's run! Turn it around!
No, this is it.
Tra-guy! But this is a zou (elephant)!
Yeah, Zou is the name of a place
that flourishes on the back
of a massive elephant.
What?! Is it alive?
It keeps moving so it'll never
be at the same location.
It's a Phantom Island.
It's not actually an island
so Log Poses won't get you here.
I've never been here before either.
It's showing its back to us.
That means Black Foot and the others
could've gotten here much earlier.
So we were chasing
an elephant that was walking away.
Yeah. Get ready to make landfall.
Can you give us some food?
For you?!
Can you give Straw Hat-ya some food?
Take everything in the food storage!
So this is Zou!
There are such unusual
things outside our country!
I wonder if Momonosuke is okay.
Hey! I heard there is a
tribe that hates humans.
Yes, it's the Mink Tribe.
They hold off humans and people say
the history of their country
goes back nearly a thousand years.
A thousand years?!
On the elephant's back?!
Does that mean that elephant has
been alive for a thousand years?!
Oh? That's...
What?! D-D-Don't tell me it's...
The Sunny!
Shut up!
So that's...
That's...
... the grand ship that carries
the sacred bodies of the Straw Hats!
The Thousand Sunny-senpai!
I feel blessed! I feel blessed!
I feel blessed!
Don't worship it!
Good! So they made it to Zou for sure.
I guess they got away
from Big Mom nicely.
There's no major damage.
Hey! Sanji!
Nami! Chopper! Brook! Momo!
And... what was the gas guy's name?
All of you senpai,
hurry up and cross over...
Oh?
Where did they go?
Oh! They're already crossing!
Luffy! Have you seen the others?
Seems like they aren't here.
What?!
I guess they all made landfall.
Yeah! Let's catch up to them quickly!
You're coming with us!
Is there anything else that you need?
I wish I could follow them
and see all the stars of the Straw Hats
from my dreams for even a little while, but...
... I don't wanna get in the way of
the adventures of those gods!
Our happiness barometer is
already at full throttle!
Next time we see you,
we'll all have abilities that
are worthy of being called
subordinates of the Straw Hats.
So if we can help you at that time,
we want the four other senpai's Divine Drops!
The Divine Drops (Autographs)
It'll be a sheer pleasure
if we can have them!
– Is that an earthworm?
– It's a snake, isn't it?
It has legs so it's a lizard.
They're totally ignoring me!
Complete disregard!
But I'm happy even with that!
So happy!
Okay, it's finished!
– What is this?
– I still think it's a snake.
I-Is that a snake?
Appear, Rising Dragon!
Dragon?!
What is this?!
Cool!
Dragon...
D-Dragon...
Some kind of pathetic creature appeared!
– Why did you...?
– Like they say, an eye for an eye.
It's cute...
All right, everyone, cling to its back!
It's gonna climb up!
Isn't it gonna fly?!
Okay! Let's go!
Good! Keep going, Dragon!
How many kilometers to go?!
I see no end up there!
Are you sure there's a country?!
Don't worry.
The Vivre Card is pointing upwards.
Oh, okay.
Dragon! You can do it!
Bye, Lome-o and everybody!
Thank you for bringing us here!
D-Did he just call my name?!
H-He called my name for the first time!
I'm happy for you, Boss!
Y-You too! Thank you very much!
Please take care on your journey!
You too! See ya!
Luffy-senpai! Take care!
Thus, the party keeps climbing up to
the top of the Phantom Island, Zou.
The Revolutionary Army's General Headquarters
Baltigo. Grand Line
Dragon-san!
Rebel armies are winning all across the world!
Monkey D. Dragon
The General Commander
of the Revolutionary Army
The fall of the Donquixote Family
had a huge impact.
This many countries were involved in the weapon trafficking.
The war situation is looking up.
But tell them not to be too
excited over their win.
The World Government won't
just sit by quietly.
Cipher Pol has been
reinforced in recent years.
So tell them to take extra care.
Yes, sir!
Dragon-san.
They say they found a
special ore in the weapons
we brought back from Dressrosa.
An ore?
Do you know of Drunken Iron Ore?
It's quite rare
and only a few countries can mine it,
so they might be able to figure out
where the weapons were actually made.
Oh, that's good news.
Yes.
You brought back our people who
went missing in Dressrosa too.
You're doing remarkably well.
Please! I couldn't do it
without Sabo-kun and Luffy-kun!
How was Robin?
I heard she was caught in Sabaody,
but that was completely false.
Yes, it was!
She was totally full of life!
Almost like...
Aren't you gonna ask me
about Luffy-kun?
Well, I've had more than enough with that.
Oh, I bet Sabo-kun told you a lot.
Anyway, Koala.
Yes.
We need their help.
Their?
Summon all the leaders of the Revolutionary
Army from all over the world!
Okay.
What?! Do you really wanna summon
all those big personalities again?!
A Sea Somewhere in the New World
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
This is Lafitte.
This... urgess.
It's me!
Burgess! It's you!
"Demon Sheriff" Lafitte
The Captain of the Fifth Ship of
The Emperor – Blackbeard's Pirate Group
We went to Dressrosa to pick you up, but you weren't there.
Yeah, sorry.
I couldn't make contact since I was
unconscious almost the whole time.
Shiliew of the Rain
The Captain of the Second Ship of
The Emperor – Blackbeard's Pirate Group
Oh, that son of a gun was alive.
Where've you been?
Where are you now?
It's all white...
It's an island as white as snow.
I snuck onto someone's ship.
Tell Captain Teach!
If we invade here now, we can
get a massive amount of weapons!
It's Commodore Teach.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Make sure to bring Doc Q too!
I'm fatally injured!
Burgess! Tell us already!
Where are you?
I don't know the name of the island.
It's a totally uncharted place.
Follow my Vivre Card and come here!
Dragon and the obnoxious Sabo are here too!
I've found it!
It's the Revolutionary Army's
general headquarters!
An Island Somewhere
Everyone's so dumb and ridiculous!
They all say the same thing!
That the members of the Whitebeard Pirates
are Whitebeard's only sons!
Edward Weevil – A Warlord
Self-proclaimed "Whitebeard Jr."
(Former Bounty: 480 Million Belly)
Mommy! Mommy!
I'm Whitebeard's son, right?!
My beard's white as well!
That's right, dear!
The Whitebeard Pirates were
just a make-bellyeve family.
You're the only biological son of
the world's strongest pirate, Whitebeard!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
And I'm...
Miss Bakkin – Weevil's Mother
Self-proclaimed "Whitebeard's Lover"
... the woman who Whitebeard loved!
So hold your head up, my treasure!
You're hurting me, Mommy!
– Look at this!
– What? Is that a mirror?
No, it's a picture of Whitebeard!
Oh, I thought that was a mirror.
You look so much like him, there's
no way you're not his son!
How can you be so silly?!
Oh, sorry, Mommy!
But I forgive you.
Because I love you!
Mommy!
Now, let's go!
Say what you've got to do!
Ummm...
I forgot.
Find the remnants of the Whitebeard Pirates
like Marco the Phoenix!
And get something back!
Your father Newgate must've left
behind a big fortune
and you're the true heir
since you're his biological son!
Oh, I see, I see.
Oh yeah! But what I really
wanna do is get revenge!
I wanna have my revenge on
Blackbeard for killing Daddy!
I'll kill him!
I won't forgive him at any price!
Silly boy! What's the
point in taking revenge?
You can't even earn one berry!
We want money!
You must inherit his fortune!
You're right, Mommy!
What's the matter, Mommy?
Doflamingo was defeated.
It's him again! Garp's grandson!
They say Marco and the others tried
to protect him in the Paramount War.
Then, maybe he knows something about Marco.
Should we go beat him up?
"Buggy Town"
False Brovado Island, New World
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
– Director Buggy!
– What do you want?!
We keep getting orders
and the Snails won't stop ringing!
Good, good!
Since they can't get weapons
from Doflamingo now,
they turned to pirate mercenaries
and we're getting a flood of calls!
We reign supreme over the military market!
Did you hear that?!
Hey, guys!
Whoever finishes eating,
go to battlefields and run
wild, and bring back booty!
Your pirating is legitimate
under the name of...
Buggy the "Star Clown" – A Warlord/Pirate
The Director of Buggy's Delivery
... the Warlord – Buggy
the "Star Clown"-sama!
Buggy's Delivery –
A Pirate Mercenary Agency
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Oh yeah, Director Buggy!
I forgot to tell you we got a call from
the S-class mercenary, Hajrudin,
and he said he wants to quit.
What?
Well, it's just one Giant, let it go.
We have four others.
I mean, all five of them want to.
What?! They're our biggest earners!
And we're so busy now!
I wanna know why!
No, you don't wanna hear it...
Say it!
Say it!!
I can't see the top yet.
I wonder how Sanji and
the others climbed this.
Are they really up there?
The "thing" that Luffy and
the rest are riding is
currently climbing the left
hind leg of the giant elephant.
It's so high! I'm scared!
My arms are exhausted! It's too much!
Don't say that, Usopp.
He's giving it all he's got.
So cute...
Kin'emon, Kanjuro.
Come to think of it, why
do you wanna go to Zou?
Oh yeah.
We owe you people a lot,
so we must tell you everything eventually.
But first, we need to feel safe.
Mm-hm. Zou was always our destination
since leaving the Land of Wano.
We want to see if Momonosuke is okay
and if another friend we
were separated from at sea,
Raizo, a ninja, has arrived here safely.
– A ninja?!
– Is he a ninja?!
What the...
A ninja... I wanna meet him!
Etetetetete...
Luffy! Look up!
Something's falling onto us!
Etetetetete...
What is that?!